{
    "question": "Bagaimana cara mengoperasikan mesin fax dan terjemahkan dalam bhasa inggris ? makasih",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<strong>Sending a fax:</strong><br><br>1.\u00a0Make sure the fax machine is plugged into a power source and also plugged into a working phone jack.<br>2.\u00a0Turn the fax machine on.<br>3.\u00a0Obtain the fax number of the destination fax machine.<br>4.\u00a0Gather the documents you want to send and put them in the order you want them to be received.<br>5.Fill out a separate piece of paper called a\u00a0coversheet\u00a0with the recipient&#039;s name, fax number/phone number, your name, your phone number, a short message and number of pages (including coversheet).<br>6.\u00a0Lay the documents face-up in the fax machine feeder tray with the coversheet on top.<br>7.\u00a0Dial the recipient&#039;s fax number (dialing instructions for\u00a0international calls)<br>8. Press the\u00a0\"fax\" or \"send\" button, depending on the particular fax machine model<br><br>Now the fax machine will scan each of the document pages into its memory. After all of the pages have been scanned, you&#039;ll hear a series of fax tones. These tones signal the \"handshake\" between the sending and receiving fax machines, establishing a communications link. Wait for a few minutes as the fax is sent. If the fax machine has a small display screen, look for a confirmation that the fax went through. Some fax machines will also print out a short confirmation report.<br><br><strong>Here&#039;s how to receive a fax:</strong><br><br>1.\u00a0Make sure the fax machine is plugged in, powered on and connected to a working phone jack.\u00a0This phone jack can either be your regular phone line or a dedicated fax line. The important thing is that the sender has the right number.<br>2.\u00a0Make sure that the fax machine has enough ink in its toner cartridge. Toner cartridges usually have some sort of indicator when toner is low. Most modern fax machines will also alert you when toner is low.<br>3.\u00a0Make sure that there&#039;s enough printer paper loaded in the fax machine&#039;s paper tray. Fan the paper (run your thumb along the bottom, separating the individual pages) to avoid paper jams in the machine.<br>4.\u00a0If there&#039;s a phone on the fax machine, the phone will ring. Don&#039;t pick it up.<br>5.\u00a0Wait for the \"handshake\" tones indicating that the fax machine is talking with the sender&#039;s machine.<br>6.\u00a0The fax machine will automatically begin to print each page of the fax.<br>7.\u00a0Check the coversheet to make sure you received as many pages as were sent.<br>8.\u00a0If it&#039;s an important document, it&#039;s office etiquette to call or e-mail the sender to confirm that you received the fax.<br><span><br>On the next page, we&#039;ll talk about how to troubleshoot common fax machine problems.<br><br><span>TRANSLATE<br><br></span><strong>\ufeff</strong></span><strong>Mengirim faks :</strong><span><br>1 . Pastikan mesin fax dicolokkan ke sumber listrik dan juga dicolokkan ke jack telepon yang berfungsi.<br>2 . Hidupkan mesin faks pada.<br>3 . Mendapatkan nomor faks dari mesin faks tujuan.<br>4 . Mengumpulkan dokumen Anda ingin mengirim dan menempatkan mereka dalam urutan yang Anda ingin mereka yang akan diterima.<br>5.Fill sepotong kertas terpisah disebut coversheet dengan nama penerima , nomor fax nomor / telepon, nama Anda , nomor telepon Anda , pesan singkat dan jumlah halaman ( termasuk coversheet ).<br>6 . Lay dokumen wajah -up di mesin fax tray feeder dengan coversheet di atas.<br>7 . Dial nomor faks penerima ( instruksi panggilan untuk panggilan internasional )<br>8 . Tekan \" fax \" atau \" kirim\" tombol , tergantung pada model mesin fax tertentu<br><br>Sekarang mesin faks akan memindai setiap halaman dokumen ke dalam memori . Setelah semua halaman telah dipindai , Anda akan mendengar serangkaian nada faks . Nada ini sinyal \" jabat tangan \" antara pengirim dan penerima mesin fax , membangun link komunikasi . Tunggu selama beberapa menit sebagai faks dikirim . Jika mesin faks memiliki layar kecil , mencari konfirmasi bahwa faks pergi melalui . Beberapa mesin faks juga akan mencetak laporan konfirmasi singkat .<br><br><strong>Berikut adalah cara untuk menerima faks :</strong><br><br>1 . Pastikan mesin fax terpasang , diaktifkan dan tersambung ke soket telepon yang berfungsi . Jack Ponsel ini dapat menjadi saluran telepon biasa atau garis faks khusus. Yang penting adalah bahwa pengirim memiliki nomor yang benar.<br>2 . Pastikan bahwa mesin faks memiliki cukup tinta dalam cartridge toner -nya . Toner biasanya memiliki semacam indikator bila toner rendah. Kebanyakan mesin fax modern yang juga akan mengingatkan Anda bila toner rendah.<br>3 . Pastikan bahwa ada kertas printer cukup dimuat dalam baki kertas mesin fax . Fan kertas ( menjalankan ibu jari Anda di sepanjang bagian bawah , memisahkan halaman individual ) untuk menghindari kertas macet di dalam mesin.<br>4 . Jika ada telepon pada mesin fax , telepon akan berdering . Jangan mengambilnya.<br>5 . Tunggu \" jabat tangan \" nada yang menunjukkan bahwa mesin faks sedang berbicara dengan mesin pengirim.<br>6 . Mesin fax akan secara otomatis mulai mencetak setiap halaman faks.<br>7 . Periksa coversheet untuk memastikan Anda menerima halaman sebanyak dikirim.<br>8 . Jika itu dokumen penting , itu etiket kantor untuk menelepon atau e-mail pengirim untuk mengkonfirmasi bahwa Anda menerima faks .<br><span><br>Pada halaman berikutnya , kita akan berbicara tentang bagaimana untuk memecahkan masalah mesin faks umum .</span></span>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0Step 1<br>Create a cover letter to make sure whom this document would be sent and whether that number is right or wrong destination. Enter you cover letter before your document info the fax machine feeder facing machine.<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0step2<br>Enter the fax number into the machine. There will be a button on the telephone numbers as a fax machine. Be careful when the numbers so you do not make mistakes.<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Step 3<br>press the submit button when you have corretly enter all the numbers into the\u00a0machine. Typically, a submit button placed on the side or buttom of the keypad.<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 Step 4<br>wait until your document prassing through the machine and collect when done.<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Step 5<br>wait until there is confirmation that you tell you whether you faks successfully sent or not.<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "apa-lawan-kata-dari-diligent-generous-friendly-easy-going-cre-436",
            "question": "apa lawan kata dari diligent, generous, friendly, easy-going, creative, two-faced, rebellious, aloof ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Diligent &gt;&lt; Lazy<br>Generous &gt;&lt; Stingy<br>Friendly &gt;&lt; Unfriendly, Hostile<br>Creative &gt;&lt; Uncreative<br>Two-faced &gt;&lt; Honest, Sincere<br>Rebellious &gt;&lt; Obedient, Docile<br>Aloof &gt;&lt; Friendly, Sociable",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terjemah-kan-ke-dalam-bahasa-indonesia-announcement-the-schoo-996",
            "question": "terjemah kan ke dalam bahasa indonesia : *announcement* the school drama club is going to organize the \"snow white\" casts audition . For those who are interested to join the audition , please come to our office on saturday , 17 september , at 2 p.m to register . The following are the requirements: (1).your latest photograph of postcard side(2). The registration form (get it in the office). The audition will be held on monday . 23 september, at 9 a.m. The list of the slected candidates will be announced in a week. We do appreciate your participation. Thank you the comittee p.s.: no change for the registration from *jangan pake google transtlet*",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "\u00a0<strong>pengumuman</strong> <br>klub drama sekolah akan mengadakan audisi \"snow white\" . Bagi siapa saja\u00a0 yang tertarik untuk bergabung audisi, silahkan datang ke kantor kami pada hari Sabtu 17 September, pukul 2 siang untuk mendaftar. Berikut ini adalah persyaratan:.<br>\u00a0(1) foto terbaru Anda sisi kartu pos <br>(2). Formulir pendaftaran (mendapatkannya di kantor). <br>Audisi akan diadakan pada hari Senin. 23 September, pukul 9 pagi Daftar calon terpilih akan diumumkan dalam seminggu. Kami menghargai partisipasi Anda. Terima kasih p.s komite: tidak ada perubahan untuk pendaftaran .",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-6-orang-di-dalam-hotel-dalam-bahasa-inggris-502",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan 6 orang di dalam hotel dalam bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Receptionist: Good morning! Welcome to Cozy Hotel. Could I help you?<br>Mr. John : Good morning! I&#039;d like to book a room for several days, please<br>Receptionist: Sure. How many days would you like to stay?<br>Mrs. John : 3 days and 2 nights, please<br>Receptionist : Certainly. We&#039;ve got room 145, 209, 310 for free. which one do you prefer?<br>Lily: Dad, I think I prefer room 310<br>Dave: Me too, dad<br>Mr. john: ok, then we&#039;d like to book room 310, please<br>Receptionist: Certainly, sir. How are you going to be paying?<br>Mrs. John: Credit card, please<br>Receptionist: Sure. Is there anything else we could help?<br>Mr. John: I think we need someone to help us bring our luggage<br>Receptionist: Sure. We&#039;ve got bellboy to help you<br>Bellboy: Good morning! <br>Mrs &amp; Mr John: Good morning! Could you help us with our luggage to room 310<br>Bellboy: Sure.<br>Receptionist: We hope you&#039;ll enjoy your stay here<br>Mrs. John: We hope so. Thank you<br>Receptionist: Your welcome<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "persamaan-simple-past-amp-present-perfect-695",
            "question": "Persamaan simple past &amp; present perfect",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "sama sama merupakan absolute relative tenses dimana sebuah kalimat terdiri dari lebih dari satu keterangan waktu.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "sama-sama menceritakan tentang masa lampau<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pengertian-globalisasi-dalam-bahasa-inggris-457",
            "question": "Pengertian globalisasi dalam bahasa inggris..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>the change when the world feels so near. because we can get much and easy connection with other people in aroud the world. it&#039;s so easy.. and it help the development proccess of culture,lifestyle. from the side of attitude. globalization can make peoples being consumtive, it will create the bad attitude like egoist, prestige,ignore ,esteem. so that, therefore globalization can make the positive, negative effect ,but thats depend on us how the way you are to face globalization</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-active-passive-pd-present-perfect-past-perfect-f-733",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat active passive pd present perfect, past perfect, future present, future past!:)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Present\nPerfect Tense\n<br>\n- Active : I\nhave called my best friend<br>- Passive :\nI have been called by my best friend\n\n<br>Past\nPerfect Tense<br>- Active : I\nhad called my best friend\n<br>\n- Passive :\nI had been called by my best friend\n<br>\nSimple\nFuture Tense<br>- Active : I\nshall call my best friend\n<br>\n- Passive :\nI shall be call by called by my best friend<br>\u00a0Future Past\nTense<br>\u00a0- Active : I\nshould call my best friend<br>\u00a0- Passive :\nI should be called by my best friend\n\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-descriptive-tentang-benda-kesayangan-936",
            "question": "CONTOH TEXT DESCRIPTIVE TENTANG BENDA KESAYANGAN",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Boneka beruang pemberian ayahnya\u00a0adalah benda kesayangan Anya. Boneka beruang atau populer dengan nama \"Teddy bear\" adalah jenis boneka\u00a0untuk anak-anak dan orang dewasa. Namanya berasal dari Theodore Roosevelt, Presiden Amerika Serikatke-26, yang nama panggilannya adalah \"Teddy\" dan senang berburu beruang. Konon suatu hari di Hotel Colorado di Glenwood Springs, Colorado, Roosevelt kembali dari perburuan yang tidak berhasil dan pegawai hotel memberinya boneka beruang tersebut. Ketika Roosevelt memberikan boneka itu kepada anaknya, Alice, ia memberinya nama Teddy. Teddy bear memiliki bulu pendek yang lembut dan biasa berwarna cokelat dan warna-warna gradasi dari cokelat. Banyak aksesoris yang bisa dipakaikan di boneka Teddy seperti pakaian dan topi.\u00a0Boneka yang berukuran mulai dari sepuluh centimeter hingga dua meter ini umum diberikan sebagai ungkapan kasih sayang.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "mengurutkan-kata-kata-ini-bgaaimana-caranya-1-if-would-an-were-m-312",
            "question": "Mengurutkan kata kata ini bgaaimana caranya    1. if-would-an-were-Mr.Alferd-a-build-he-orphanage-billionaire\r\n2. a-don't-must-better-you-this afternoon-see-you-docyor-feel-it\r\n3. renovate-gets-Father-from-house-he-office-bonus-the-his-will-if-a\r\n4. if-she-a-our-Ayu-have-our-joined-for-group-problem-would-solution",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. mr. alfred would build an orphanage if he were a billionaire\n2. you must see doctor this afternoon if you dont feel better\n3. father will renovate his house if he gets a bonus from the office\n4. ayu would have a solution for our problem if she joined our group",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. Mr. Alfred would build an orphanage if he were a billionare.<br>2. You must see a doctor this afternoon if you don&#039;t feel it better<br>3. Father will renovated the house if he gets a bonus from his office<br>4. Ayu would have a solution for our problem if she joined our group<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatkan-naskah-drama-bahasa-inggris-untuk-7-orang-cewek-4-orang-581",
            "question": "buatkan Naskah drama bahasa inggris untuk 7 orang. cewek 4 orang, cwok 3 orang....\r\ntolong :)\u00a0 bebas, tpi jangan pnjng.panjang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Kiki: Hello,Good Morning all\nTerusin Aja yah Tema nasjah englus itu yg bagus best friend in my heart",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kalau-nama-lain-dari-v1-v2-v3-dan-ving-apa-701",
            "question": "Kalau nama lain dari V1, V2, V3, dan Ving apa?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "v1 : bare infintive<br>v2 : past tense<br>v3: past participle<br>ve/es : additional infinitive<br>ving : present participle<br><br>maksudnya ini ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}